export const chapter = "Chapter - 22: Essay writing ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "What is Ratan Tata's contribution to the Tata Group?",
          optionA: "He increased unethical practices.",
          optionB: "He scaled the ladder of success through corrupt means.",
          optionC:
            "He ensured Tata's tradition of business ethics and commitment to society remains intact.",
          correctAnswer:
            "C) He ensured Tata's tradition of business ethics and commitment to society remains intact.",
        },
        {
          question: "What is celebrated on the first day of Holi?",
          optionA: "Playing with colors",
          optionB: "Raising a bonfire",
          optionC: "Sprinkling gulal",
          correctAnswer: "B) Raising a bonfire",
        },
        {
          question: "In which months is wheat harvested in India?",
          optionA: "January-February",
          optionB: "March-April",
          optionC: "May-June",
          correctAnswer: "B) March-April",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the main purpose of terrorism according to the passage?",
          optionA: "To promote peace and harmony",
          optionB: "To instill fear and fulfill demands",
          optionC: "To foster equality and brotherhood",
          correctAnswer: "B) To instill fear and fulfill demands",
        },
        {
          question: "What profession does the author aspire to pursue?",
          optionA: "Doctor",
          optionB: "Engineer",
          optionC: "Teacher",
          correctAnswer: "C) Teacher",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which cricket format is described as quick encounters and frequent upsets?",
          optionA: "Test cricket",
          optionB: "One-day cricket",
          optionC: "Twenty-20 cricket",
          correctAnswer: "C) Twenty-20 cricket",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What are some problems associated with city life mentioned in the text?",
          optionA: "Limited opportunities",
          optionB: "Air and noise pollution",
          optionC: "Unplanned drainage system",
          correctAnswer: "B) Air and noise pollution",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What does positive thinking entail according to the passage?",
          optionA: "Thinking for the welfare of society",
          optionB: "Thinking for personal gain at the expense of others",
          optionC: "Thinking negatively about oneself",
          correctAnswer: "A) Thinking for the welfare of society",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Who is remembered for his positive qualities but misused them?",
          optionA: "Ratan Tata",
          optionB: "Hitler",
          optionC: "Abhinav",
          correctAnswer: "B) Hitler",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the ultimate aim of positive thinking?",
          optionA: "Personal gain through manipulation",
          optionB: "Achieving what is good and noble",
          optionC: "Ignoring societal welfare",
          correctAnswer: "B) Achieving what is good and noble",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "Ratan Tata was born on __________, 1937 to Naval Tata and Sooni Tata.",
          options: ["28 November", "28 December", "28 January"],
          correctAnswer: "28 December",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ratan Tata finished his secondary school at the Cathedral and John Cannon School in __________.",
          options: ["Delhi", "Mumbai", "Kolkata"],
          correctAnswer: "Mumbai",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Abhinav, the friend visited by the narrator, invited him to his house many times, and finally, the narrator visited him last __________.",
          options: ["Monday", "Saturday", "Wednesday"],
          correctAnswer: "Saturday",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Holi is celebrated on the last day of the Hindi month of __________.",
          options: ["Kartik", "Phalgun", "Chaitra"],
          correctAnswer: "Phalgun",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Wheat is grown in almost all countries of the world, including the USA, Canada, Argentina, and __________.",
          options: ["China", "India", "Australia"],
          correctAnswer: "India",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Terrorism is the gravest menace faced by almost all countries of the world today, as evident from attacks on twin-towers in the US on 11 September, 2001, and the attack on the Parliament of India on __________.",
          options: [
            "13 December, 2000",
            "13 December, 2001",
            "13 December, 2002",
          ],
          correctAnswer: "13 December, 2001",
        },
        {
          question: "A teacher is the __________ of a nation's destiny.",
          options: ["destroyer", "creator", "observer"],
          correctAnswer: "creator",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Twenty-20 cricket is likely to eclipse the popularity of __________ cricket.",
          options: ["Test", "One-day", "Five-day"],
          correctAnswer: "One-day",
        },
        {
          question:
            "City life has both attractive and ugly aspects, as cities provide dwellers with unlimited opportunities in the form of education and employment, but also face problems like overcrowding, __________, and air pollution.",
          options: ["water scarcity", "earthquakes", "traffic congestion"],
          correctAnswer: "traffic congestion",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Positive thinking entails thinking for the welfare of society and employing one's prowess in striving to achieve what is good and __________.",
          options: ["noble", "evil", "mundane"],
          correctAnswer: "noble",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "Ratan Tata was born on 28 December, 1937.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Abhinav, the friend visited by the narrator, invited him to his house many times, and finally, the narrator visited him last Saturday.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Holi is celebrated on the last day of the Hindi month of Phalgun (March).",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Terrorism has become a global menace today.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Twenty-20 cricket is likely to eclipse the popularity of Test cricket.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "City life provides dwellers with unlimited opportunities in the form of education and employment.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Positive thinking entails thinking for the welfare of society.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Wheat is next only to rice as the most popular staple diet in India.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The attacks on twin-towers in the US on 11 September, 2001, point to the immense strength of peaceful organizations.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "A teacher is the architect of a nation's destiny.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
